

 $\searrow$ 

rupaktyagi21@gmail.com



8077285046



Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh



linkedin.com/in/rupaktyagi21



github.com/Rupaktyagi

### **SKILLS**

Java

Data Structures and Algorithms

GitHub

JavaScript

MvSOI

### **LANGUAGES**

English

Limited Working Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Cricket

Kabaddi

Animal Welfare

# Rupak Tyagi

**Backend Developer** 

Adaptable and Accountable team player, driven to deliver the best in any situation. A passionate Backend Developer with proficiency in Java, JavaScript, SQL, Data Structure And Algorithms. Looking forward to utilizing current skillset and experience of working of projects.

Remote

Bijnor

Greater Noida,India

### **EDUCATION**

### **Backend Development**

Masai School

03/2022 - 08/2022

Courses

Backend development, DSA

## **Bachelor of Technology**APJ Abdul kalam Technical University

08/2016 - 08/2020

Courses

Mechanical Engineering

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Graduate Engineer Trainee**Le Mei Plastic Manufacturing Private Limited

12/2020 - 02/2022 A manufacture of Smartphone middle frame

**Assistance Engineer**Le Mei Plastic Manufacturing Private Limited

12/2021 - 02/2022 Grater Noida ,India

### **PROJECTS**

#### Hindustan Times Clone

- News based app that provide national, international and current affairs
- Development along with a team of 5 member in one week
- Teck stack: JavaScript , HTML, CSS

### Solar Electric Car

A vehicle which run with electric power